Associates Of The Department Of Entomology Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
Associates Of The Department Of Entomology Archives
1920-1986
ENTAR.001722
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
4
one filing cabinet
Miscellaneous Archives from associated people with in the department of Entomology.
Division of Entomology, Yale Peabody Museum
Biographical Sketch
see individual series
Description of the Material
Miscellaneous Archives from associated people with in the department of Entomology, including those of G. Evelyn Hutchinson, Frank Young and Charles Hodge.
Connecticut; USA; Correspondence; Field notebooks; Photographs; Yale Peabody Museum; Yale University
- G. Evelyn Hutchinson, Series I
  Scope and Contents
  Archives of G. E. Hutchinson.
  - Biographical Material. EST number of items= 30+., 001730
  - Hutchinson Fund. History of and paperwork regarding Hutchinsons Fund. EST number of items = 15+., 001732
  - Memorial Service. EST number of items=10+., 1991; 001731
  - Reprints. Reprints of published works by G.E. Hutchinson. EST number of objects = 30+., 001733
    - Original reprint from C. L. Remington library of Hutchinson 1959 American Naturalist paper "Homage to Santa Rosalia, or, why are there so many kinds of animals?", 1959-1959; 002777
  - Research archives. Research archives including associated specimen material., 002780
    - Original drawer from G. E. Hutchinson's collection, containing eight corixids that formed part of the research material behind his 1959 American Naturalist paper "Homage to Santa Rosalia, or, why are there so many kinds of animals?", 1959-1959; 002779
- Frank N. Young, Series II
  Frank N. Young archives, all are on Tropisternus Breeding Data.
  - Beetle Breeding Data. EST number of items = 200+. Index cards located in library., 002735
  - Tropisternus Breeding Data. EST number of objects =50+., 001735
- F.R. Arnhold, 1920-1958; Series III
  Archives of F.R. Arnhold, mostly field notebooks.
  - Field Notebooks. EST number of items = 10., 1920-1958; 001737
- Charles Hodge, Series IV
  Archives of Charles Hodge
  - Beetle Notebooks., 1965-1972; 001739
- T.D. Sargent, Series V
  - Catocala. EST number of items = 30+,., 1961-1977; 001741
  - Miscellaneous Field Notes., 1986; 001743
  - Taxon Summaries. EST number of items = 40+., 1982-1985; 001742